DECEMBER 2020
2020년 12월
BOXING JINNAM
복싱진남
Excuse me?
실례합니다?
Put on your mask.
마스크를 쓰세요.
Come on, let's go.
자, 가자.
A mask is required on the bus.
버스 내에서는 마스크가 필수입니다.
Party.
파티.
First put on your mask.
먼저 마스크를 착용하세요.
Don't tell me what to do!
나에게 무엇을 해야할지 말하지 마세요!
- There's a sanction... - I'll decide whether to impose it!
- 제재가 있는데... - 부과 여부는 제가 결정하겠습니다!
- Don't tell me what to do! - All right.
- 나에게 무엇을 해야할지 말하지 마세요! - 괜찮은.
Do you drive the bus? So go ahead and drive!
버스를 운전하시나요? 그러니 가서 운전하세요!
Misery!
불행!
First put on your mask.
먼저 마스크를 착용하세요.
- Enough! - Stop it.
- 충분한! - 그만해요.
- There are other passengers. - Leave me!
- 다른 승객도 있어요. - 날 떠나요!
Hands off, you wretch!
손 떼라, 이 불쌍한 놈아!
- Hands down! - Excuse me.
- 손을 아래로! - 실례합니다.
And what do you want?
그리고 너가 원하는게 뭐야?
I think it's better if he walks home.
내 생각엔 그 사람이 집에 걸어가는 게 더 좋을 것 같아.
- Bad... - I'm sorry.
- 안됐어... - 미안해요.
Ugly piece of...
못생긴 조각...
I'm sorry.
죄송합니다.
I am sorry.
미안해요.
Again, sorry.
다시 한 번 죄송합니다.
No, I don't want to hurt her.
아니, 난 그녀를 다치게 하고 싶지 않아요.
Curse!
저주!
Damn you!
젠장!
My apologies.
사과드립니다.
What a pain you are.
당신은 정말 고통 스럽습니다.
Yes, damn it.
응, 젠장.
I apologize for what happened.
일어난 일에 대해 사과드립니다.
- Thank you. - No problem.
- 감사합니다. - 괜찮아요.
Thanks, you did well.
고마워요, 잘 했어요.
- A thousand thanks! - Thank you!
- 정말 고마워요! - 감사합니다!
I am sorry.
미안해요.
I didn't know it would take this long.
이렇게 오래 걸릴 줄은 몰랐어요 .
I'm sorry this happened.
이런 일이 발생해서 죄송합니다.
I'll try for next month.
다음 달에도 노력하겠습니다.
Can you wait another month?
한 달 더 기다릴 수 있나요?
I'll give you everything back.
나는 당신에게 모든 것을 돌려 줄 것입니다.
Yes, then I'll think about next month.
네, 그럼 다음 달에 생각해 보겠습니다.
Okay thanks.
괜찮 감사.
I FOLLOW
나는 팔로우한다
In the midst of the crisis due to the COVID pandemic
코로나19 팬데믹으로 인한 위기 속에서
a stopped construction site puts public safety at risk.
중단된 건설 현장은 공공 안전을 위험에 빠뜨립니다.
The construction of the building was blocked twice
건물 건설이 두 번 차단되었습니다
because a bricklayer was positive.
한 벽돌공이 긍정적이었기 때문입니다.
The construction company in charge has failed
담당 건설업체가 실패했습니다
and this havoc remains which disfigures the city.
도시를 훼손하는 이러한 혼란은 여전히 ​​남아 있습니다 .
Seoul must act immediately to find a solution.
서울은 해결책을 찾기 위해 즉각 행동해야 합니다 .
In the United States, they laid off more than 3.5 million employees
미국에서는 350만명 이상의 직원을 해고했다.
of hotels since mid-year.
올해 중반 이후 호텔 수.
I say this because for at least three or four years
이렇게 말하는 이유는 적어도 3 ~4년 동안은
there is no foreign company that will want to buy the hotel.
호텔을 사고 싶어하는 외국 회사는 없습니다 .
- And not even Korean. -You say it as if it were a fact.
- 한국인도 아니고요. -그는 그것이 사실인 것처럼 말합니다.
I have friends who will be future leaders
미래의 리더가 될 친구들이 있어요
of the 50 most important companies.
가장 중요한 50개 기업 중 하나입니다.
We talked about it and this is the conclusion,
우리는 그것에 대해 이야기했고 이것이 결론입니다.
so I would say it's true.
그래서 나는 그것이 사실이라고 말하고 싶습니다.
On the contrary,
반대로,
it's a true fact.
그것은 사실이다.
You did well to deal with me, Vice President.
부통령님, 저와 거래를 잘 하셨습니다.
Director Hong.
홍 감독.
Our bank financed the property with 400 billion.
우리 은행은 부동산에 4000억 달러를 조달했습니다.
Saying it returns 300 billion is not a deal.
3000억을 돌려준다는 말은 거래가 아니다.
You will have to suffer some losses.
당신은 약간의 손실을 입어야 할 것입니다.
How do you do business?
사업은 어떻게 하시나요?
I don't do business,
나는 사업을 하지 않는다,
I'm a banker.
나는 은행가입니다.
Therefore, director, vice president,
그래서 이사, 부사장,
the reason you are here is...
당신이 여기 있는 이유는...
Yes.
예.
The mayor wants to finish the construction as soon as possible
시장님은 하루라도 빨리 공사를 끝내고 싶다고 하십니다.
for security reasons.
보안상의 이유로.
But he's as stubborn as a donkey!
하지만 그는 당나귀처럼 고집이 세다!
Vice President, are you calling me an ass?
부통령님, 저를 바보라고 부르시나요?
Tell me when you weren't stubborn.
고집이 없었을 때 말해주세요.
I'm sorry for my late.
늦어서 미안해요.
President Kim Myeong-gil, who I told you about before.
아까 말씀드렸던 김명길 회장님 .
Welcome.
환영.
Representative Seo Woo-hyeon introduced us ,
서우현 대표님이 소개해주신 ,
an acquaintance of the mayor.
시장의 아는 사람.
Kim Myeong-gil.
김명길.
KIM Myeong-GIL
김명길
I contact you separately.
별도로 연락드리겠습니다.
Right.
오른쪽.
Kim Myeong-gil.
김명길.
Can I ask you what you do?
무슨 일을 하시는지 물어봐도 될까요?
Especially about investments.
특히 투자에 대해서는요.
When people ask me, I try to help however I can.
사람들이 나에게 물어보면 나는 최선을 다해 도와주려고 노력한다.
Do you have a credit granting business?
신용공여 사업을 하고 계십니까?
Excuse me, but did you bring us a loan shark?
실례합니다만, 사채업자를 데려오셨나요?
Chairman Kim deals with various things.
김 회장은 다양한 일을 하고 있다.
It's not a place for loan sharks, don't you think?
사채업자들이 있을 곳은 아니지 않나요?
You are President Hong Woo-geun's eldest son , yes?
홍우근 회장님 장남 이시죠?
As a young man, I worked for President Bang in Myeong-dong.
저는 젊었을 때 명동에서 방회장 밑에서 일했습니다.
She won't remember him because he was small.
그녀는 그가 어렸기 때문에 그를 기억하지 못할 것이다 .
When the financial crisis hit,
금융위기가 닥쳤을 때,
the Iil Group, open for 50 years, almost went bankrupt
50년 창업 한 일그룹 , 부도 직전
because he didn't have six billion.
왜냐하면 그에게는 60억이 없었기 때문입니다.
So, President Hong Woo-geun
그럼 홍우근 대표님
went to ask my boss, President Bang, for help.
상사인 방 대표님께 도움을 청하러 갔습니다 .
He begged him to save the company at any cost.
그는 어떤 대가를 치르더라도 회사를 구해 달라고 간청했습니다.
President Bang was moved by his passion and sincerity.
방 대표는 열정과 성실함에 감동받았다 .
I took a bag with six billion won in cash and came to his house.
나는 현금 60억이 담긴 가방을 들고 그의 집으로 찾아왔다.
I remember his mother preparing me
그의 어머니가 나를 준비시킨 것을 기억한다
some excellent melons to express gratitude.
감사의 마음을 표현하기 위한 훌륭한 멜론 .
Dirty money does not exist. It can be used with criminal intent
더러운 돈은 존재하지 않습니다. 범죄 의도로 사용될 수 있어
but when the cause is right, it's clean money.
하지만 원인이 옳다면 그것은 깨끗한 돈입니다.
I'm here to help.
저는 도와드리려고 왔습니다.
If you update me on the negotiations...
협상에 대해 알려주시면..
They have two different numbers in mind.
그들은 두 가지 다른 숫자를 염두에 두고 있습니다.
- We were talking about it. - I understand. How much is it?
- 우리는 그것에 대해 이야기하고 있었어요. - 이해합니다. 얼마인가요?
One hundred billion won.
천억 원.
Do you intend to personally follow the hotel's activities, director?
호텔 활동을 직접 따라갈 생각이신가요 , 이사님?
I did a master's degree in hotel management in Switzerland
저는 스위스에서 호텔경영학 석사학위를 취득했습니다.
and I worked in Hong Kong.
그리고 저는 홍콩에서 일했어요.
I understand. He is very prepared.
이해합니다. 그는 매우 준비되어 있습니다.
Would you be okay with me making an investment?
제가 투자해도 괜찮겠습니까 ?
By how much?
얼마만큼?
Beh,
베,
100 billion missing, I would invest that amount.
1000억 누락, 그 금액만큼 투자하겠습니다.
I also invest more, if necessary.
필요하다면 더 투자하기도 합니다.
And the conditions?
그리고 조건은?
Well, there are only three.
글쎄요, 세 개밖에 없어요.
I would like to build a small casino on the top floor of the hotel.
호텔 꼭대기층에 작은 카지노를 짓고 싶습니다 .
His dream is to manage a hotel,
그의 꿈은 호텔경영,
mine is to open a casino.
내 것은 카지노를 여는 것입니다.
Then, you will help me make sure there is a lounge bar on the ground floor.
그런 다음 1층에 라운지 바가 있는지 확인하는 데 도움을 주세요 .
Finally, if there were such a thing as COVID again ,
마지막으로 또 코로나 같은 일이 생긴다면,
we will give the hotel spaces for quarantine
격리를 위해 호텔 공간을 제공하겠습니다
of those who have no money, for free.
돈 없는 사람들은 공짜로.
In difficult times, we must help each other.
어려운 시기에는 서로 도와야 합니다.
This is how we create a better world.
이것이 우리가 더 나은 세상을 만드는 방법입니다.
I'm willing
나는 기꺼이
to pay the 100 billion quota also tomorrow morning.
내일 아침에도 1000억 할당량을 지불합니다 .
How did it go?
어떻게 됐나요?
- Well. - Did they take the bait?
- 잘. - 미끼를 물었나요?
- Yes. - Hurray!
- 네 - 만세!
And go! Now I have to think about how to furnish the bar.
그리고 가세요! 이제 바를 어떻게 꾸밀지 고민해야 합니다 .
You don't go to the bar to admire the decor.
장식을 감상하기 위해 바에 가지 않습니다 .
We go to meet girls. Take care of finding beautiful girls.
우리는 여자를 만나러 간다. 아름다운 소녀를 찾아보세요.
Mind your own business, idiot.
네 일이나 신경쓰라고, 바보야.
Maybe someone as beautiful as you could also speak well.
어쩌면 당신만큼 아름다운 사람 도 말을 잘 할 수 있을 겁니다.
What do you know? Imbecile!
당신은 무엇을 알 수 있습니까? 바보!
I want to clean my face.
얼굴을 깨끗하게 하고 싶어요.
Ecco.
에코.
Let's go.
갑시다.
E al Seongeun Building?
이알성은빌딩?
The tenants have no ties to the police or prosecutor's office.
임차인은 경찰이나 검찰청과 아무런 관련이 없습니다 .
Not even friends and relatives?
친구나 친척도 아니고요?
It only happened once, President.
딱 한번 있었던 일입니다, 대통령님.
Maybe they have a policeman lover.
어쩌면 그들은 경찰관 애인이 있을지도 모릅니다.
You do your job and he stays calm.
당신은 당신의 일을 하고 그는 침착함을 유지합니다.
You think about your work.
당신은 당신의 일에 대해 생각합니다.
Jang-do,
장도,
address your sister-in-law with respect.
당신의 처제에게 존경심을 가지고 말하십시오.
I apologize.
사과드립니다.
Apologize to me, asshole!
나한테 사과해, 이 새끼야!
The asshole apologizes, ma'am.
그 새끼가 사과했어요, 부인.
Let's move, I want to drink.
가자, 마시고 싶어.
Yes, President.
네, 대통령님.
Welcome to the 2020 KBFC Rookies Tournament.
2020 KBFC 루키 토너먼트에 오신 것을 환영합니다.
The arena is usually packed with spectators
경기장은 보통 관중들로 가득 차 있습니다.
who is cheering, but because of COVID,
누가 응원하고 있는데 코로나 때문에
today the public is not there.
오늘은 대중이 거기에 없습니다.
It's a sad atmosphere.
슬픈 분위기네요.
Yes, there are usually always fans
네, 보통 항상 팬이 있어요
for all the athletes, but now there is only silence.
모든 운동선수들에게, 이제는 침묵만이 있을 뿐입니다.
The third round of Hong Woo-jin's fight begins.
홍우진의 3차전이 시작된다.
A clash between middleweights.
미들급 간의 충돌.
Hong Woo-jin in rosso,
로소를 입은 홍우진,
mentre Jung Jae-hun è in azzurro.
정재훈 멘토 è in azzurro.
Forza.
포르자.
- Nice series of shots. - Yes
- 멋진 일련의 사진입니다. - 예
Hong leans against the ropes.
홍이 밧줄에 기대어 있다.
Taunt the opponent after hitting them.
상대를 때린 후 도발합니다.
It's true, but the opponent doesn't get upset.
그렇지만 상대는 화를 내지 않습니다.
- "Prova a colpirmi." - Sì.
- "Prova a colpirmi." - 그래.
"Dai, provaci."
"다이, 프로바치."
Che botta!
체보타!
Forza.
포르자.
- A clean jab. - And another one in the face!
- 깨끗한 잽입니다. - 그리고 얼굴에 또 하나!
He knocked him out! Hong Woo-jin!
그가 그를 쓰러뜨렸습니다! 홍우진!
A double right followed by a one-two.
이중 권리 다음에 1-2가 이어집니다.
Yes, what great footwork. He's a real talent.
예, 정말 멋진 발놀림이군요. 그는 정말 재능이 있습니다.
Ed è KO!
에드 에 KO!
The next match is Kim Gun-woo vs. Kin Rae-hyeon.
다음 경기 는 김건우 vs. 킨래현입니다.
Kim Gun-woo, la promessa, è in azzurro.
김건우, la promessa, è in azzurro.
Kim Gun-woo waits for the opportunity with his guard up.
김건우는 방심한 채 기회를 기다린다.
Bravo!
브라보!
- What a shot! - He's on his knees!
- 정말 멋진 일이네요! - 그는 무릎을 꿇었습니다!
A precision shot to the solar plexus...
태양 신경총에 대한 정밀한 사격...
- It matches if conclude which. - Sì.
- 어느 쪽인지 결론을 내리면 일치합니다. - 그래.
Un colpo ed è KO.
KO에 의해 편집되었습니다.
Kim Gun-woo continua a vincere con un colpo.
김건우가 계속 해서 승리를 거두었다.
- It's flawless. - Yes
- 흠잡을 데가 없습니다. - 예
He is an athlete who promises well.
그는 좋은 약속을 하는 운동선수입니다.
The situation is heating up.
상황이 가열되고 있습니다.
- It's on the corner. - He closed it.
- 모퉁이에 있어요. - 그가 문을 닫았습니다.
He pushed him to the ground. She threw him to the ground.
그는 그를 땅바닥으로 밀었습니다. 그는 그것을 땅에 던졌습니다.
È fallo.
안녕하세요.
- It's true. - It was him...
- 사실이에요. - 그 사람이었어요...
- He is too agitated. - Yes
- 그는 너무 불안해요. - 예
- Boxing! - Force!
- 복싱! - 힘!
He moves his hair, Hong is really histrionic.
그는 머리를 흔들고, 홍은 정말 히스테리적이다.
- Already. - Provokes the opponent.
- 벌써요. - 상대방을 도발합니다.
Schivata.
쉬바타.
Guardate come schiva!
가드가 와요 시바!
Again... And it hits! He goes down.
다시 한 번... 그리고 성공했습니다! 그는 쓰러졌습니다.
It's Hong Woo-jin's specialty.
홍우진의 특기입니다.
- Yes. - Double jab and hook!
- 예. - 더블 잽과 훅!
Hong Woo-jin, il marine.
홍우진, 일마린
Hong Woo-jin vince di nuovo.
홍우진이 새로운 사람이 되었습니다.
Adesso, Kim Gun-woo contro Lee Yong-gyu.
아데소, 김건우가 이용규를 콘트롤한다.
Kim Gun-woo, in red, has a massive physique.
빨간 옷을 입은 김건우 의 육중한 체격
- Yes. - Nice dodge.
- 예. - 잘 피했어요.
- His strength is melee. - Yes
- 그의 강점은 근접전입니다. - 예
He knows how to handle himself well in hand-to-hand combat.
그는 백병전에서 자신을 잘 다루는 방법을 알고 있습니다.
One shot and dodge.
원샷과 회피.
- Liver shot! - Knocked out with one blow!
- 간 주사! - 일격에 기절!
- A win for the fegato. - Yes.
- Fegato의 승리입니다. - 네.
At the time, I was good like that too.
그때 나도 그게 좋았다.
- Are you OK? - Yes.
- 괜찮으세요? - 예.
- Indeed you won the gold. - It's true.
- 정말 금메달을 땄군요. - 사실이에요.
Kim Gun-woo e Hong Woo-jin.
김건우와 홍우진.
- Well. - Who takes home the trophy?
- 잘. - 트로피는 누가 가져가나요?
Small movements, short punches, use your hips!
작은 움직임, 짧은 펀치, 엉덩이를 활용하세요!
Watch out for the left hook. It goes down hard.
레프트 훅을 조심하세요. 열심히 내려갑니다.
SOUTH KOREA NAVIES 1216
한국 해군 1216
But I'm a Marine.
하지만 저는 해병대입니다.
Watch out for the left hook.
레프트 훅을 조심하세요.
I am an invincible marine. Invincible!
나는 무적의 해병이다. 무적!
If he beats you bloody and you cry, I'll kill you.
그 사람이 널 때리고 울면 죽여버릴 거야.
- Force!
- 힘!
Good match. At the corners.
좋은 경기. 모서리에.
Fantastic encounters so far.
지금까지의 환상적인 만남입니다.
Kim Gun-woo, the promise, fights differently.
약속 김건우, 다르게 싸운다.
Exactly. Kim Gun-woo is good at attacking his opponent.
정확해요. 김건우는 상대 공격을 잘한다.
Sì.
그렇습니다.
Instead, Hong Woo-jin keeps his distance and has a phenomenal counterattack.
대신 홍우진은 거리를 유지하며 경이로운 역습을 펼치고 있다.
Yeah, Hong Woo-jin has fun during meetings.
네, 홍우진 씨는 회의할 때 재미있어요.
Sì.
그렇습니다.
Instead the opponent is serious and does not provoke...
대신 상대가 진지하고 도발하지 않는데...
Attack! He's cornering him!
공격하라! 그 사람이 그를 궁지에 몰고 있어요!
Will Hong Woo-jin scam her?
홍우진은 그녀를 속일 것인가?
He managed to free himself.
그는 스스로 자유로워졌습니다.
- Yes, Hong Woo-jin is very fast. - Exactly.
-네, 홍우진은 엄청 빠릅니다. - 바로 그거예요.
But Kim Gun-woo is also a middleweight...
근데 김건우도 미들급 선수인데...
And try a powerful hook!
그리고 강력한 훅을 시도해 보세요!
- Yes. - He blocked it. Now the stomach.
- 네 - 그 사람이 차단했어요 이제 위.
Kim Gun-woo si difende bene.
김건우씨는 이의를 제기했습니다.
- Yes. - It's a rock
- 예. - 바위예요
His guard is up.
경비원이 출동했습니다.
Montante!
몬탄테!
- Here. -He scored.
- 여기요. - 맞았습니다.
Yes, and so.
그렇습니다.
Enthralling clash.
매혹적인 충돌.
Hook! And dodge!
훅! 그리고 피하세요!
Ora tocca a Hong Woo-jin.
홍우진을 만나보세요.
Hong Woo-jin continua a pressare.
홍우진이 계속해서 기자회견을 하고 있다.
- Left hook! - An accident. Will he recover?
- 레프트 훅! - 사고. 회복될까요?
- And it goes down. - It's on the carpet!
- 그리고 그것은 무너졌습니다. - 카펫 위에 있어요!
- È al tappeto. - Due...
- È al tappeto. - 마감...
With a blow to the stomach the consequences come later.
배에 타격을 가하면 결과는 나중에 나옵니다.
- It's true. - It takes five seconds.
- 사실이에요. - 5초 정도 걸립니다.
Alzati! Woo-jin!
알자티! 우진!
Six seven...
여섯 일곱...
- He gets up. - Yes.
- 일어나요. - 예.
- He has already recovered. - Yes...
- 그는 이미 회복되었습니다. - 예...
Sì.
그렇습니다.
This is farà male.
이것은 정말 남성적입니다.
- You'll hear it soon. - Right.
- 곧 듣게 될 것입니다. - 그렇죠.
Forza.
포르자.
Forza!
포르자!
Come on, get on with it.
자, 계속하세요.
Son of a bitch.
개자식.
Come on, come on!
어서, 어서!
Will it fall?
떨어질까요?
- Kim Gun-woo ci pensa. - Forza!
- 김건우 씨 펜사. - 포르자!
He's gone! Will he strike?
그가 사라졌어요! 그가 공격할 것인가?
Stop! One two...
멈추다! 하나 둘...
It must have hurt a lot.
많이 아팠겠군요.
- The tactic went wrong. - KO.
- 전술이 잘못되었습니다. - KO.
Esatto.
에사토.
Kim Gun-woo scored and ended the match,
김건우가 득점해 경기를 마무리했고,
again with his single shot, this time to the side.
다시 한번 그의 싱글 샷으로, 이번에는 옆으로.
Are you OK?
괜찮으세요?
I have tarnished the honor of the Marines.
나는 해병대의 명예를 훼손했습니다.
Everyone goes down with a shot to the liver.
모두가 간에 주사를 맞고 쓰러집니다 .
I'm leaving.
나는 떠난다.
And to eat?
그리고 먹을까?
There's still COVID.
아직 코로나가 있습니다.
I just lost, at least buy me lunch.
방금 길을 잃었어요. 최소한 점심이라도 사주세요.
Go home and order.
집에 가서 주문하세요.
Ciao.
챠오.
What? Why? What?
무엇? 왜? 무엇?
Shall we eat something?
우리 뭐 좀 먹을까?
Why should I come with you?
내가 왜 당신과 함께 가야 합니까?
I wanted to go eat bacon. Do you want?
베이컨 먹으러 가고 싶었는데 원하시나요?
Do you feel sorry for me?
나한테 미안해?
No.
아니요.
Tell that to the losers you knocked out.
당신이 쓰러뜨린 패자에게 그 사실을 말해주세요.
They returned home.
그들은 집으로 돌아왔습니다.
Ugh.
윽.
- The prize was ten million? - Yes.
- 상금이 천만 달러였나요? - 예.
So why bacon? Let's have a steak.
그렇다면 왜 베이컨일까요? 스테이크를 먹자.
- I only want to spend 50,000 won. - Why?
- 5만원만 쓰고 싶어요. - 왜?
I have to give the rest to my mother.
나머지는 어머니께 드려야 해요.
- Do you owe her money? - No.
- 그 사람한테 빚진 게 있어요? - 아니요.
Then why?
그렇다면 왜?
I pay you the bar rent.
나는 당신에게 바 임대료를 지불합니다.
You are a good son.
당신은 좋은 아들입니다.
If you spend 10,000 more,
10,000원 ​​더 쓰시면
there is a buffet that costs 29,000 won per head.
1인당 29,000원인 뷔페가 있어요 .
It's great, they have Korean beef.
좋아요, 한국산 쇠고기가 있어요.
- Really? Where? - I'm joking, stupid.
- 정말? 어디? - 농담이야, 바보야.
How do they serve it at 29,000 won?
29,000원에 어떻게 제공하나요?
Have you only done boxing in life?
살면서 권투만 해본 적이 있나요?
It's good. He takes out another 10,000 won.
좋다. 그는 10,000원을 더 꺼낸다.
Let's go.
갑시다.
Got a strong left hook, huh?
강력한 레프트 훅이 있죠?
I used to train with a tire when I worked in the landfill.
저는 매립지에서 일할 때 타이어를 끼고 훈련하곤 했습니다 .
Only the left one?
왼쪽만?
Why only the left one?
왜 왼쪽만?
Did you only train with your left foot?
왼발로만 훈련하셨나요?
With both of them.
둘 다.
And why is the left strong?
그리고 좌파가 강한 이유는 무엇입니까?
- The right is stronger. - Why did you use the left?
- 오른쪽이 더 강해요. - 왜 왼쪽을 사용했나요?
I couldn't find the right moment for the right.
나는 적절한 순간을 찾지 못했습니다 .
What a bully.
정말 깡패입니다.
How come?
왜요?
Because you say you knock out with the left.
당신이 왼쪽으로 녹아웃한다고 말했기 때문입니다 .
Today, yes.
오늘은 그렇습니다.
You see? You're a bully.
알겠어요? 당신은 깡패입니다.
No not at all.
전혀 그렇지 않습니다.
Turn the meat.
고기를 뒤집으세요.
It takes another 30 seconds.
30초가 더 걸립니다.
Turn it over immediately.
즉시 뒤집으십시오.
No, I worked in a place like that. I know meat.
아니, 나도 그런 곳에서 일했어요. 나는 고기를 안다.
Man, you've worked all over the place.
이봐, 당신은 여기저기서 일했어요.
- Are you poor? - Yes, my family lost everything.
- 당신은 가난합니까? - 네, 우리 가족은 모든 것을 잃었어요.
How come?
왜요?
My father was a researcher in a large company.
아버지는 대기업의 연구원이셨습니다 .
He sued for unfair dismissal, but lost four years later.
그는 부당해고를 이유로 소송을 제기했으나 4년 만에 패소했다.
Legal fees turned into debt.
변호사 비용이 빚으로 바뀌었습니다.
With big companies you lose. The rich always win.
대기업에서는 패배합니다. 부자는 항상 승리합니다.
That's how it is.
그렇다니까.
- What other jobs have you done? - Of everything.
- 또 어떤 일을 했나? - 모든 것.
I mostly made deliveries with my mother.
저는 주로 어머니와 함께 배달을 했어요.
You are an eclectic worker.
당신은 절충주의적인 일꾼입니다.
You can do anything, you're really good at it.
당신은 무엇이든 할 수 있어요, 당신은 정말 잘해요.
Turn the meat with your right hand.
오른손으로 고기를 뒤집으세요.
When did you start boxing?
복싱은 언제 시작했나요?
More or less three years ago.
대략 3년 전입니다.
- When? - After the military.
- 언제? - 군대 다녀온 후.
I started in sixth grade.
저는 6학년 때부터 시작했어요.
My father was in the national team.
아버지가 국가대표였거든요.
Well, that's cool. What is his name?
글쎄요. 멋지네요. 그의 이름은 무엇입니까?
Hong Seong-geun. Bronze at the Barcelona Olympics.
홍성근. 바르셀로나 올림픽 동메달.
- Ah here. - Do you know him?
- 아 여기요. - 그를 아니?
No.
아니요.
Many boxers know him.
많은 권투 선수들이 그를 알고 있습니다.
I am sorry.
미안해요.
Did your father teach you?
아버지가 가르쳐 주셨나요?
- We're not very close. - Why?
- 우리 별로 안 친해요. - 왜?
He's never happy with what I do.
그 사람은 내가 하는 일에 결코 만족하지 않아요.
At my age he had won bronze,
내 나이에 그는 동메달을 땄고,
he judges me based on his successes.
그는 자신의 성공을 기준으로 나를 판단합니다.
At that time,
그때에,
won the bronze medal at 25?
25살에 동메달을 땄나요?
No, a 27.
아니요, 27입니다.
How old are you?
몇 살이에요?
Twenty seven.
스물 일곱.
Well, I apologize then.
그럼 사과하겠습니다.
I'm 25 years old. I am very sorry.
저는 25세입니다. 너무 미안 해요.
What the hell, you idiot.
뭐야, 이 바보야.
Do you forgive me.
용서해 주겠니.
- Oh! - Yes?
- 오! - 예?
Behave now, huh?
이제 행동해, 응?
- Certainly. - Understood?
- 틀림없이. - 이해했다?
Yes.
예.
Girala.
히랄라.
No, it takes another minute.
아니요, 1분 정도 더 걸립니다.
- It's ready, turn it over! - Not yet.
- 준비됐어요, 뒤집어주세요! - 아직 아님.
Damn, you're so stubborn.
젠장, 당신은 너무 고집스럽군요.
The military?
군대?
Yes, I said I boxed after the military.
네, 군대를 다녀온 뒤 복싱을 했다고 했어요 .
I know.
알아요.
I wanted to know what force I was in.
나는 내가 어떤 세력에 속해 있는지 알고 싶었습니다.
- Be more careful. - I was in the Marines.
- 좀 더 조심하세요. - 저는 해병대에 있었습니다.
Come on!
어서 해봐요!
I'm a Marine too.
나도 해병이다.
With what degree?
어느 정도?
1207°.
1207°.
Watch out! I 1216th, sir!
조심해! 저는 1216번째입니다!
Sit down again.
다시 앉으세요.
What are you doing? Come on!
뭐하세요? 어서 해봐요!
- I sit down when she does too. - Ah...
- 그 사람이 앉으면 나도 앉는다. - 아...
Marine Kim Gun-woo, signore.
김건우 해병대장.
- Yes? - And where, sir?
- 예? - 어디죠?
In the first department.
첫 번째 부서에서.
Me too! In what battalion, sir?
저도요! 어느 대대에서요?
- Reconnaissance. - Crazy.
- 정찰. - 미친.
I wanted to get in there too, but I couldn't, sir.
저도 거기 들어가고 싶었는데 들어갈 수 없었어요 선생님.
The Pride of the Marines: Reconnaissance Wing.
해병대의 자부심: 정찰단.
Reconnaissance!
정찰!
Listen, I want to address you firsthand, without formalities.
들어보세요, 형식적인 절차 없이 직접 여러분에게 말씀드리고 싶습니다 .
I understand, sir.
이해합니다.
Let's be on first terms.
첫 번째 조건을 살펴 보겠습니다.
Let's address each other on a first-name basis, sir.
선생님, 이름을 중심으로 서로 호칭을 합시다.
Come on...
어서 해봐요...
Dai.
다이.
Yes,
예,
I am very proud to be a Marine.
나는 해병대원이라는 사실이 매우 자랑스럽습니다.
Why?
왜?
I was a bit of a delinquent in Incheon,
인천에서는 좀 불량이었는데,
but in the Marines and I met good people
하지만 해병대에서 좋은 사람들을 만났어요
and I realized I was wrong.
그리고 나는 내가 틀렸다는 것을 깨달았습니다.
Training hard together, I really enjoyed it.
함께 열심히 훈련해서 정말 즐거웠습니다.
Delicious.
맛있는.
Waking up early, going for a run, sweating
일찍 일어나서 달리고, 땀을 흘리고
and help each other wash.
그리고 서로 도와서 씻는다.
- Woo-jin. - Yes?
- 우진. - 예?
- Are you one of those crazy marines? - No.
- 당신도 그 미친 해병 중 하나인가요? - 아니요.
Break in.
침입하다.
As?
처럼?
It's like a steak.
마치 스테이크 같아요.
Truly?
진심으로?
I'll show you a thing.
제가 한 가지 보여드리겠습니다.
- Put three pieces. - Yes.
- 3개를 넣어주세요. - 예.
- A little spicy.
- 조금 매워요.
And kimchi too.
그리고 김치도요.
- Marine Kim Gun-woo, sir. - Yes?
- 김건우 해병대장님. - 예?
It's the bomb, right?
폭탄이군요, 그렇죠?
Would you like something to drink?
마실 것좀 드실 래요?
Why? Are you afraid of gaining weight?
왜? 살이 찌는 것이 두렵나요?
You perfectionists are two balls.
당신 완벽주의자들은 두 개의 공입니다.
Ma'am, excuse me!
부인, 실례합니다!
A bottle of beer and some soju, please!
맥주 한 병과 소주 한 잔 주세요!
How much do the shoes cost?
신발 가격은 얼마인가요?
- 1,200,000 won. - Really?
- 1,200,000원. - 정말?
They cost the same as the bar rent.
바 임대료와 가격이 같습니다.
You're such a moron.
당신은 정말 바보입니다.
They are fake.
그들은 가짜입니다.
They seem real.
진짜인 것 같아요.
The fake ones have a shiny tip.
가짜는 끝 부분에 반짝이는 부분이 있습니다.
The real ones are suede. The finishing is terrible.
진짜는 스웨이드예요. 마무리가 형편없습니다.
If you want them, I find them better than the real ones.
당신이 원한다면, 나는 그것이 진짜 것보다 더 낫다고 생각합니다.
- Really? - Like "really"?
- 정말? - "정말" 같은 거요?
As beautiful as the real ones, there are none.
진짜만큼 아름다운 것은 없습니다.
Let's meet, so I'll teach you how to live.
만나자, 사는 법을 가르쳐 줄게.
You worked too hard.
당신은 너무 열심히 일했습니다.
Do you know anything about it? It's quite widespread.
그것에 대해 아는 것이 있나요? 꽤 널리 퍼져 있습니다.
“Special COVID Loans.”
“특별 코로나 대출.”
I worked in this industry when I needed money.
나는 돈이 필요할 때 이 업계에서 일했습니다 .
- Already. - Those who are desperate are easier to fool.
- 이미. -절박한 사람은 속이기 쉽습니다.
COVID has pushed many to desperation.
코로나19는 많은 사람들을 절망에 빠뜨렸습니다 .
The loan sharks are rubbing their hands.
사채업자들이 손을 비비고 있습니다.
How come?
왜요?
Since they're all trying to pay the rent,
다들 집세를 내려고 하니까.
the loan sharks are there waiting to take all the money.
사채업자들이 모든 돈을 가져가려고 기다리고 있습니다.
My mother is in trouble with the rent of the bar.
우리 엄마는 술집 임대료 때문에 고민이 많으세요 .
The bar yields less than half of what it used to,
바의 생산량은 예전보다 절반도 안 됩니다.
but the landlord wants the same rent.
하지만 집주인은 같은 임대료를 원합니다.
If we close now, moving will cost us more.
지금 문을 닫으면 이사 ​​비용이 더 많이 들게 됩니다.
Let's hold on, otherwise we have to return it to its previous state.
기다리지 않으면 이전 상태로 되돌려야 합니다.
Second.
두번째.
Next time I'll take you somewhere more beautiful.
다음에 는 더 아름다운 곳으로 데려가겠습니다.
The steak?
스테이크?
There is a butcher's shop that also serves as a restaurant.
레스토랑 겸 정육점도 있습니다 .
Do you really mean it, yes?
정말 진심이에요, 그렇죠?
Do you think I would tell a lie to a higher ranking Marine?
내가 더 높은 직급의 해병대에게 거짓말을 할 것이라고 생각합니까 ?
- In my opinion, yes. - You do not believe me?
- 제 생각에는 그렇습니다. - 당신은 저를 믿지 않는?
You've already done this several times.
당신은 이미 이 작업을 여러 번 수행했습니다.
Yes, but I was joking, stupid.
응, 하지만 농담이었어, 멍청아.
From now on, no lies.
이제부터는 거짓말이 아닙니다.
All right.
괜찮은.
I am sorry.
미안해요.
I'm dismayed.
나는 실망했다.
This month I thought I would make it,
이번 달에는 성공할 수 있을 거라 생각했는데,
but I didn't succeed.
하지만 나는 성공하지 못했습니다.
Yes, I'll invent something for next month .
네, 다음 달에 쓸 뭔가를 고안해 보겠습니다 .
I'm sorry.
죄송합니다.
- We will talk later. - Mom.
- 나중에 얘기하자. - 엄마.
I'll call you tomorrow morning.
내일 아침에 전화할게요.
Tesoro!
테소로!
How good!
정말 좋아요!
You were amazing today!
오늘 정말 대단했어요!
- Did you see the meeting? - Of course yes.
- 회의 봤어? - 물론 예.
The commentators complimented you.
평론가들이 당신을 칭찬했습니다.
- Truly? - They said you were flawless.
- 진심으로? - 당신이 완벽하다고 하더군요.
I want to see it too.
나도 보고 싶다.
- Mom, wait. - Yes.
- 엄마, 잠깐만요. - 예.
You've been very good.
당신은 아주 잘 지냈어요.
Second.
두번째.
What are they?
그들은 무엇인가?
The prize money. Pay us the rent.
상금. 우리에게 집세를 지불해주세요.
Cielo.
시엘로.
I can't take them.
나는 그것을 가져갈 수 없습니다.
No, I won to give them to you.
아니요, 당신에게 주기 위해 제가 승리했습니다.
Let's first return the money we took from uncle.
우선 삼촌한테 받은 돈을 돌려주자 .
What?
무엇?
How do you know?
어떻게 알 수 있나요?
The uncle is also in difficulty. Let's give them back quickly.
삼촌도 힘들어요. 빨리 돌려보내자.
All right.
괜찮은.
But I'll give it back to you with interest.
하지만 관심을 가지고 돌려드리겠습니다.
- All right. - Thank you.
- 괜찮은. - 감사합니다.
Let's go, mom.
가자, 엄마.
Oh God, it's cold. Force.
맙소사, 추워요. 힘.
Have you already eaten?
벌써 식사하셨나요?
Yes, certainly.
예 당연 하죠.
With who?
누구 랑?
With the one I challenged in the final.
제가 결승에 도전한 것과 함께요.
The one with curly hair?
곱슬 머리를 가진 사람?
Yes him.
응, 그 사람.
You ate?
당신은 먹었나요?
Yes, I already ate.
응, 난 이미 먹었어.
President.
대통령.
How is it going?
어떻게 지내요?
Tenants owe money to banks and finance companies,
임차인은 은행과 금융회사에 돈을 빚지고 있으며 ,
as she said.
그녀가 말했듯이.
By next week they will already be our customers.
다음 주까지 그들은 이미 우리 고객이 될 것입니다.
Beh,
베,
can you this week?
이번주에 할 수 있어?
Congressman Seo wants us to kick them out now.
서 의원은 이제 그들을 쫓아내길 원한다.
Of course, President.
물론이죠, 대통령님.
Well, let's hurry then.
그럼 서두르자.
Jun-min, selling is important.
준민아, 파는 게 중요해.
Yes, sir.
알겠습니다.
Beom.
범.
Let's get ready.
준비하자.
I'm Yoo In-yeong, I work for Smile Capital.
스마일캐피탈에 근무하는 유인영 입니다 .
We are a financial company
우리는 금융회사입니다
which has the state certification of excellence.
국가로부터 우수성 인증을 받은 제품입니다.
- Do you have some time to talk? - Certain.
- 잠시 이야기 나눌 시간 있나요? - 확실한.
Lately, the number of customers has decreased, right?
최근에는 손님이 줄었지요?
Already.
이미.
You have a mortgage of 40 million won, right?
담보대출 이 4천만원 있잖아요 ?
Yes.
예.
If you sign, we'll take care of repaying your debt today.
서명하시면 오늘 빚을 갚아드리겠습니다.
We have a rate of 5%, which is lower than the bank's 7%.
우리의 금리는 5%로 은행의 7%보다 낮습니다.
And how do you make money?
그리고 돈은 어떻게 버나요?
Beh, sa,
베, 사,
the government has approved special aid measures
정부는 특별 지원 조치를 승인했습니다
to support small businesses in difficulty due to COVID.
코로나로 어려움을 겪는 중소기업을 지원하기 위해
We won the contract and thus we lowered the interest.
우리는 계약을 따내서 이자를 낮췄습니다.
A 2% difference is not a small thing.
2%의 차이는 작은 것이 아닙니다.
In times like these, you only win by holding on.
이런 때에는 버티는 것만으로도 승리할 수 있습니다.
COVID will pass sooner or later.
코로나19는 조만간 지나갈 것입니다.
We would like to help you keep your business open.
우리는 귀하의 사업이 계속 열려 있도록 돕고 싶습니다 .
It's an advantage for us,
그게 우리한테는 장점이에요.
but above all it is good for her.
하지만 무엇보다도 그것은 그녀에게 좋은 일이다.
- Thank you. - I'm the one who thanks you.
- 감사합니다. - 나는 당신에게 감사하는 사람입니다.
SMILE CAPITAL FIRMA YOON SO-YEON
스마일캐피탈 퍼마 윤소연
SPARK BOXING GYM
스파크 복싱 체육관
What?
무엇?
They ate fried chicken at the gym last night.
그들은 어젯밤에 체육관에서 프라이드치킨을 먹었습니다.
It seems that someone was positive.
누군가 긍정적인 것 같더군요.
Do I have to take a swab?
면봉을 가져와야 하나요?
Non serve.
제공되지 않습니다.
You had the meeting yesterday. Why are you already at the gym?
당신은 어제 회의를 가졌습니다. 왜 벌써 체육관에 왔어요?
- Per allenarmi. - Gun-woo.
- 알레나르미당. - 건우.
Get some rest.
좀 쉬.
And then what do I do?
그러면 나는 어떻게 해야 합니까?
If you do something you don't rest.
무슨 일을 하면 쉬지 않습니다.
Don't do anything and rest.
아무것도 하지 말고 쉬세요.
All right.
괜찮은.
GU-NOO
구누
Hello, what are you doing?
안녕하세요 지금 뭐하는거야?
sleep
잠
Come?
오다?
Dormo.
도르모.
I don't hear well.
잘 들리지 않습니다.
I said I'm sleeping.
자고 있다고 했어요.
I'm sleeping.
내가 자고 있어요.
Do you want to train?
훈련하고 싶나요?
No.
아니요.
I am getting bored.
점점 지루해지고 있어요.
Ugh. You're already nagging first thing in the morning.
윽. 당신은 이미 아침에 일어나자마자 잔소리를 하고 있습니다.
Come on, let's meet.
자, 만나자.
I'll send you the address, come here.
주소 보내드릴 테니 이리 오세요.
All right.
괜찮은.
Fuck!
못쓰게 만들다!
Hey! Stop!
여기요! 멈추다!
Asshole!
항문!
Everything OK?
모든 것이 괜찮아?
One moment...
잠시만...
What do you want?
당신은 무엇을 원하세요?
Why are you following me?
왜 나를 따라오나요?
Who sent you?
누가 당신을 보냈나요?
I wanted to help.
나는 돕고 싶었습니다.
What?
무엇?
Who were you helping?
누구를 돕고 있었나요?
I thought someone was chasing that man.
누군가가 그 사람을 쫓고 있는 줄 알았어요 .
- Fuck! - What's up?
- 젠장! - 무슨 일이야?
That asshole is pretending.
그 새끼는 그런 척 하는 거야.
- As? - Mind your own business.
- 처럼? - 니 일이나 신경써.
- All right. - What an idiot you are.
- 괜찮은. - 정말 바보 같군요.
How come here?
여기 어떻게 왔나요?
Mi-yeon's surgery yesterday went well.
어제 미연이의 수술은 무사히 끝났습니다.
Really? How is he now?
정말? 그는 지금은 어떤가요?
Well. She is recovering.
잘. 그는 회복 중입니다.
It's thanks to you, President.
덕분입니다, 대통령님.
If you hadn't helped us,
당신이 우리를 도와주지 않았다면,
Mi-yeon would have died.
미연이는 죽었을 것이다.
Have.
가지다.
My husband recently moved to a large company
남편이 최근 대기업에 이직했어요
and they paid him severance pay.
그리고 그에게 퇴직금을 지급했다.
I came as soon as we received them
받자마자 왔어요
because I wanted to return them to him immediately.
왜냐하면 나는 그것들을 즉시 그에게 돌려주고 싶었기 때문입니다.
There was no need to give them to me right away.
당장 나에게 줄 필요는 없었습니다.
Think about urgent things.
긴급한 일을 생각해 보세요.
No, President, please accept them.
아니요, 대통령님, 받아주세요.
So I'm calmer.
그래서 나는 더 차분해졌습니다.
Thank you, President.
감사합니다, 대통령님.
I thank you from the bottom of my heart.
진심으로 감사드립니다.
Thank you very much.
매우 감사합니다.
MI-YEON'S MOTHER 14 APRIL 2018 20 MILLION
미연 어머니 2018년 4월 14일 2천만
KOREAN ANTIQUES
한국 골동품
I saw that bastard Yang Jae-myeong, he said he was broke,
저 양재명 새끼를 봤는데 망했다고 하더군요
but I got this from him.
하지만 나는 그에게서 이것을 얻었습니다.
It is worth more than 20 million won.
가격은 2000만원이 넘습니다.
So what?
그래서 뭐?
I gave Yang Jae-myeong ten million.
양재명한테 천만 줬어요.
Here are the interests.
여기에 관심분야가 있습니다.
Does it hurt?
그거 아프니?
Shit. Yang Jae-myeong and I got into a fight.
똥. 양재명 씨와 제가 싸웠어요.
By the way, we really need to talk now.
그런데, 우리 지금 정말 얘기를 해야 해요.
Do you want a sweet?
달콤한 것을 원하시나요?
Don't try to change the subject.
주제를 바꾸려고 하지 마세요.
Are you thinking of quitting?
그만둘 생각이 있나요?
Stop what?
뭘 멈춰?
To make interest-free loans.
무이자 대출을 하려고 합니다.
We don't make money.
우리는 돈을 벌지 않습니다.
In what sense?
어떤 의미에서?
I always pay you a 30% commission.
나는 항상 당신에게 30%의 수수료를 지불합니다.
Not me. I mean you, grandfather.
나는 아니다. 내 말은, 할아버지.
Do you know Mi-yeon's mom?
미연 엄마를 아시나요?
Yes why?
예, 왜요?
She came first and gave me everything back in cash.
그녀는 먼저 와서 나에게 모든 것을 현금으로 돌려주었습니다.
With interest?
관심이 있습니까?
Hyeon-ju.
현주.
A sick little girl was operated on and is doing well.
아픈 어린 소녀가 수술을 받았고 잘 지내고 있습니다.
I gave him the money
나는 그에게 돈을 주었다
and they have not mortgaged the house as security for the loan.
그리고 그들은 대출에 대한 담보로 그 집을 저당잡히지 않았습니다 .
The child has a home to return to when they discharge her.
아이에게는 퇴원 후 돌아갈 집이 있습니다.
We saved a family.
우리는 가족을 구했습니다.
It is the most valuable interest rate in the world.
세상에서 가장 가치 있는 이자율입니다 .
And oh well...
그리고 아 글쎄...
However, when I was looking for Yang Jae-myeong I found out
그런데 양재명을 찾다가 알게 됐어요.
that he and his gang dress like homeless people,
그와 그의 갱단은 노숙자처럼 옷을 입고,
they steal the identity of real homeless people and make loans in their names.
그들은 실제 노숙자의 신분을 도용 하고 그들의 이름으로 대출을 해준다.
What people are they?
그들은 어떤 사람들입니까?
They were in prison with Yang Jae-myeong, some convicted felons.
그들은 일부 중죄인 양재명과 함께 감옥에 갇혔습니다 .
And you decided to go anyway?
그런데도 가기로 결정하셨나요?
Are you coming too next time?
다음에도 너도 올 거야?
Look, I'll do some research, maybe I'll find something interesting.
보세요, 제가 조사를 좀 해볼께요. 어쩌면 흥미로운 것을 찾을 수도 있을 것 같아요.
Don't take unnecessary risks.
불필요한 위험을 감수하지 마십시오.
All right.
괜찮은.
DIRECTOR MOON GWANG-MU
Director 문광무
Pronto.
조속히.
Should I call at another time?
다른 시간에 전화해야 할까요?
No, just tell me.
아니, 그냥 말해 보세요.
I wanted to ask you a favor. You have to find me someone.
나는 당신에게 부탁을하고 싶었습니다. 나한테 누군가를 찾아줘야 해.
Yes, just a moment.
네, 잠시만요.
Tell me everything.
나에게 모든 것을 말해주세요.
"A good person,
"좋은 사람,
security expert,
보안 전문가,
better if he knows the world of loans."
그가 대출의 세계를 안다면 더 좋을 것입니다."
All right, President.
좋습니다, 대통령님.
I will find the most qualified candidates.
나는 가장 적격한 후보자를 찾아낼 것이다.
Thanks for the help.
도와 주셔서 감사합니다.
Sissir
시시르
Watch out!
조심해!
Mayweather is the best.
메이웨더가 최고입니다.
But Mayweather seems more like a businessman than a boxer.
하지만 메이웨더는 권투선수라기보다는 사업가에 더 가까운 것 같습니다.
Exact. He does it for the money, but he's really good at it.
정확한. 그 사람은 돈 때문에 하는 일 이지만 정말 잘해요.
In my opinion, he made real billions.
제 생각에는 그는 실제로 수십억 달러를 벌었습니다.
Does money matter to you?
돈이 당신에게 중요합니까?
What matters more than money?
돈보다 더 중요한 것은 무엇입니까?
The heart of a boxer.
권투선수의 심장.
What's up?
무슨 일이야?
- Come on, what is it? - Nothing, sorry.
- 어서, 그게 뭐야? - 아무것도 아니에요, 미안해요.
Well, you know...
너도 알듯이...
You got all serious suddenly.
갑자기 심각해졌네요.
I did not expect.
나는 기대하지 않았다.
Tell me about the boxer's heart.
권투선수의 마음에 대해 말해 보세요.
I think Manny Pacquiao is the best.
매니 파퀴아오가 최고인 것 같아요.
Bye bye!
안녕!
Dad! Pacquiao! Pa!
아빠! 파퀴아오! 아빠!
Come on, can you let me talk once without interrupting me?
자, 방해하지 않고 한 번만 얘기하게 해줄 수 있나요?
Excuse me, sir. I won't interrupt her anymore.
실례합니다. 나는 더 이상 그녀를 방해하지 않을 것입니다.
I admire Pacquiao's heart. He never gives up.
나는 파퀴아오의 마음을 존경한다. 결코 포기하지 않습니다.
This is true, but Mayweather made more money.
이것은 사실 이지만 Mayweather는 더 많은 돈을 벌었습니다.
I bet that, thanks to Pacquiao, many have started dreaming of being boxers.
파퀴아오 덕분에 많은 사람들이 복서의 꿈을 가지기 시작했을 것 같아요 .
It happened to me.
나에게 일어난 일입니다.
It's the person I want to become.
제가 되고 싶은 사람이에요.
One that proves that dreams do come true
꿈이 실현된다는 것을 증명하는 것
if you put will and passion into it.
의지와 열정을 쏟는다면.
It's very windy today.
오늘은 바람이 많이 불네요.
This is the true heart of the boxer,
이것이 복싱선수의 진심이다.
it is the hope we instill in those who watch our meetings.
그것은 우리의 집회를 지켜보는 사람들에게 우리가 심어주는 희망입니다 .
- The heart... - Ah, it's ready.
- 심장이... - 아, 준비됐어요.
Let's eat.
먹자.
Ecco.
에코.
- Are good? - Yes, excellent.
- 좋다? - 네, 훌륭해요.
But what work do you do?
그런데 무슨 일을 하시나요?
I taught gymnastics at a friend's kindergarten.
나는 친구의 유치원에서 체조를 가르쳤습니다.
A kind of master.
일종의 주인.
Well, it doesn't suit you.
글쎄, 그것은 당신에게 적합하지 않습니다.
How, sorry? Children love me.
어떻게요? 죄송해요? 아이들은 나를 사랑합니다.
In the morning I taught and in the afternoon I trained.
오전에는 가르치고 오후에는 훈련을 했습니다.
Since school closed, I've been in trouble.
학교가 문을 닫은 이후로 나는 어려움을 겪었습니다.
Do you want to deliver parcels with me? Deliveries are going swimmingly.
저와 함께 소포를 배달하시겠습니까? 배송이 순조롭게 진행되고 있습니다.
- Do they pay well? - Yes.
- 돈을 잘 주나요? - 예.
If we commit ourselves,
우리가 스스로 헌신한다면,
we also earn 200,000 won a day.
우리도 하루에 20만원씩 벌어요.
Truly?
진심으로?
With deliveries you do cardio,
배달을 통해 유산소 운동을 하고,
you use muscles that you don't use with boxing and your balance improves.
복싱에서는 사용하지 않는 근육을 사용하게 되고 균형 감각이 향상됩니다.
Two birds with one stone, man.
일석이조, 두 마리의 새.
- Three pigeons. - Meaning what?
- 비둘기 세 마리. - 무슨 뜻?
You make gains, you do cardio and you improve your balance.
당신은 이득을 얻고, 유산소 운동을 하며 , 균형 감각을 향상시킵니다.
Cardio and balance count for one.
유산소 운동과 균형은 하나로 계산됩니다.
No, they are two different things.
아니요, 둘은 서로 다른 것입니다.
Ugh.
윽.
You didn't represent Korea at the Super Series,
슈퍼시리즈에 한국 대표로 출전하지 않으셨는데요 .
since you won the rookie tournament?
신인 토너먼트에서 우승한 이후로요 ?
Yes, but it was postponed due to COVID.
네, 하지만 코로나19로 인해 연기되었습니다.
Cabbage. But how much longer will it take?
양배추. 하지만 얼마나 더 걸릴까요?
I can not do anything about it.
나는 그것에 대해 아무것도 할 수 없습니다.
But I'm always ready to fight.
하지만 나는 언제나 싸울 준비가 되어 있습니다.
Sai,
사이,
you have the heart of a boxer.
당신은 권투 선수의 마음을 가지고 있습니다.
Dai.
다이.
- Come here, Pacquiao. - Now?
- 이리 오세요, 파퀴아오. - 지금?
Forza!
포르자!
Why did you hit me?
왜 나를 때렸어요?
I'm sorry.
죄송합니다.
Come on, come here. Stop that.
어서, 이리로 오세요. 그만.
Come here, Kim Gun-woo!
이리와요 김건우님!
Hey, Kim Gun-woo! Come here!
안녕하세요, 김건우님! 이리 오세요!
Let's have a nice toast!
맛있게 건배하자!
- Hello! - Cine Cine!
- 안녕하세요! - 씨네 씨네!
And now the highlight! The most spectacular performance!
그리고 이제 하이라이트! 가장 화려한 퍼포먼스!
In-beom smashes the watermelon!
인범이 수박을 으깬다!
Come on, how much do you bet?
자, 얼마를 걸겠어요?
A million who can't make it!
성공하지 못하는 백만 명!
I bet you three million that he can do it!
그가 해낼 수 있다는 데 300만 달러를 걸겠습니다!
If I win the pot, I'll offer you everything!
내가 이기면 너에게 모든 것을 주겠다!
Beom.
범.
I know you can crack it, but I'll bet four million on no.
당신이 그것을 해독할 수 있다는 것은 알지만, 그렇지 않은 경우에는 400만 달러를 걸겠습니다.
- Mr. In-beom! - Go ahead!
- 인범씨! - 어서!
He rocked it!
그는 그것을 흔들었다!
Buy your snacks!
간식을 사세요!
Let's buy some food!
음식을 좀 사보자!
Fantastic!
환상적입니다!
It worked out well for me, didn't it?
나한테는 잘 됐지, 그렇지?
Silence!
고요!
Yes, mayor.
네, 시장님.
Yes.
예.
Yes, I see.
그래, 난 참조.
I tell him.
나는 그에게 말한다.
Good evening to you.
안녕하세요.
The mayor will support
시장님이 응원하겠습니다
his casino project.
그의 카지노 프로젝트.
I have prepared a small gift
작은 선물을 준비했어요
on your birthday, Mr. Park.
생일 축하해요, 박 선생님.
Open it.
열어 봐.
That's 3.7kg of gold.
3.7kg의 금입니다.
Say. Park,
말하다. 공원,
turtles are clean, no one will understand where they come from.
거북이는 깨끗해서 그들이 어디서 왔는지 아무도 이해하지 못할 것입니다.
I give them to him with hope
나는 희망을 가지고 그에게 그것을 준다
that this relationship will be profitable for a long time.
이 관계가 오랫동안 수익성이 있을 것이라는 것입니다.
I would be truly grateful if you decided to accept them.
받아들이기로 결정해 주시면 진심으로 감사하겠습니다 .
It will not always remain with the Municipality.
항상 지방자치단체에 남아 있는 것은 아닙니다.
I know he has big ambitions.
나는 그가 큰 야망을 가지고 있다는 것을 알고 있습니다.
If he wants to get to the Blue House
청와대에 가고 싶다면
and the National Assembly, she will need money.
국회도 돈이 필요할 것이다.
Let's make an alliance.
동맹을 맺자.
He will have my full support, always.
그는 언제나 나의 전적인 지지를 받을 것이다.
My money has never let me down.
내 돈은 나를 실망시킨 적이 없습니다.
But what are you doing?
그런데 뭐하는 거야?
Be careful. We'll take her home.
조심하세요. 우리는 그녀를 집으로 데려갈 것이다.
Let's go.
갑시다.
When are you taking care of Congressman Seo's building?
서 의원 건물은 언제 관리하시나요 ?
It depends on the stores, but by Friday.
점포에 따라 다르지만 금요일까지입니다.
Between all of them, they owe about 20 million in interest.
그들 모두 사이에 약 2천만 달러의 이자를 빚지고 있습니다.
With the right push, they will go away.
올바른 푸시를 사용하면 사라질 것입니다.
People tend to give up
사람들은 포기하는 경향이 있다
if he sees his shop devastated when he goes to work.
그가 출근할 때 그의 가게가 황폐화된 것을 본다면 .
I will do so, President.
그렇게 하겠습니다, 대통령님.
Mr. Jung isn't well, he's not here tonight.
씨. 정씨는 몸이 좋지 않아 오늘 밤 여기에 없습니다.
I tell him to send about fifteen men.
나는 그에게 15명 정도를 보내라고 말했습니다 .
Beom takes care of finishing.
범이가 마무리를 맡는다.
Do we give them weapons?
그들에게 무기를 주나요?
They are not needed.
필요하지 않습니다.
Tell him to put on his suit and mask.
그에게 양복 과 마스크를 착용하라고 말하세요 .
President, five are enough.
대통령님, 5명이면 충분합니다.
The president will have his reasons.
대통령도 나름의 이유가 있을 것이다.
It is true.
그건 진실이야.
I'm wrong, for sure.
나는 틀렸다.
Here we go again with you two assholes.
여기 두 멍청이와 함께 다시갑니다.
Come on, let's concentrate. So?
자, 집중하자. 그래서?
Where do we want to start?
우리는 어디에서 시작하고 싶나요?
Salve.
고약.
He didn't keep his promise.
그는 약속을 지키지 않았습니다.
Come?
오다?
He had to pay a commission
그는 수수료를 지불해야 했어요
in exchange for a lower rate.
그 대가로 더 낮은 가격으로.
What?
무엇?
He had to pay a fee on the loan
그는 대출에 대한 수수료를 지불해야 했다
which is 10% of the sum
이는 합계의 10%입니다.
within 24 hours of signing the contract. It's in the contract.
계약서 서명 후 24시간 이내. 계약서에 있습니다.
She couldn't do something that easy
그녀는 그렇게 쉬운 일을 할 수 없었어
and the interest on the commission amounts to 40 million.
수수료에 대한 이자는 4천만 달러에 달합니다.
And then his credit rating got worse and the rate is now 20%.
그러다가 신용등급이 점점 나빠져서 지금은 20%가 됐습니다.
Sit down,
앉아,
we set out with the best intentions.
우리는 최선의 의도로 출발했습니다.
But she ruined everything!
하지만 그녀는 모든 것을 망쳤습니다!
What will he do now?
그는 이제 무엇을 할 것인가?
Is there any interest money?
이자도 있나요?
I'll call the police.
경찰에 전화할게요.
Police?
경찰?
Yes.
예.
Hate.
싫어하다.
Ciao, mamma.
챠오, 엄마.
Hello where are you?
안녕 어디야?
I'm almost there.
거의 다 왔어요.
Okay, I'm at the bar.
알겠습니다. 바에 있어요.
There are some strange people here...
여기 이상한 사람들이 있어요...
Strange people? Who I am?
낯선 사람들? 나는 누구입니까?
I am...
그래요...
Mamma?
엄마?
Smash everything!
모든 것을 부수세요!
Where do you think you're going, idiot?
어디로 갈 것 같아, 바보야?
Where are you going? Get out of my way, you idiot!
어디 가세요? 비켜, 이 바보야!
Go away, I told you!
가세요, 내가 말했잖아요!
Do not try...
시도하지 마...
- What happens? Take it. - Idiot.
- 무슨 일이야? 가져. - 바보.
- And who would this asshole be? - Hey you, asshole!
- 그러면 이 새끼는 누구일까요? - 이봐, 멍청아!
Stop him, come on!
그를 멈춰라, 어서!
Asshole!
항문!
- Damn! - Fuck!
- 젠장!
- Hey, over here. - Shit!
- 이봐, 여기야.
Cursed!
저주 받은!
Asshole!
항문!
Mom, are you okay?
엄마, 괜찮아요?
Yes.
예.
Did you get hurt?
다쳤어요?
I am fine.
괜찮아요.
Who are you?
누구세요?
Why did you do this at the bar?
술집에서 왜 그랬어요?
I asked you who you are.
나는 당신이 누구인지 물었습니다.
Calm down, kid.
진정해, 꼬마야.
Your mother borrowed money from us.
네 엄마가 우리한테 돈을 빌렸어.
What do you want?
당신은 무엇을 원합니까?
May he give them back to us.
그가 그것들을 우리에게 돌려주기를 바랍니다.
Pay the damage to the bar first.
바에 대한 손상을 먼저 지불하십시오.
Beom.
범.
Everything is fine. Stay here for a moment.
모든 것이 괜찮습니다. 잠시만 여기 있어 주세요.
Gun-woo.
건우.
Gun-woo!
건우!
Gun-woo, no!
건우, 안돼!
Beom.
범.
Sai,
사이,
I like those who have determination.
나는 결단력이 있는 사람을 좋아한다.
- Those who have determination can do everything. - Cursed.
- 의지가 있는 사람은 무엇이든 할 수 있다. - 저주받았어요.
Do you want to work for me?
나를 위해 일하고 싶나요?
Of...
의...
Subtitles: Giada Riva
자막: 지아다 리바